addicted2success.com 2019-06-25

# Privacy Policy | Addicted 2 Success

We take your privacy very seriously and are committed to being transparent with how we use your information. This website and any of our services and sites directing you to this Privacy Policy are controlled by Addicted2Success. (collectively “we” or “us”).

Our Privacy Policy explains:

  * What information we collect and why we collect it.
  * How we use that information.
  * The choices we offer, including how to access and update information.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at: info@addicted2success.com.

Addicted2Success (“Company”, “we”, or “us”) respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it through this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy governs your access to and use of addicted2success.com, including any content, functionality and services offered on or through addicted2success.com (the “Website”), whether as a guest or a registered user.

When accessing the Website, the Company will learn certain information about you, both automatically and through voluntary actions you may take, during your visit. This policy applies to information we collect on the Website and in email between you and the Website.

Please read the Privacy Policy carefully before you start to use the Website.

 **What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

 _Information We Collect Through Automatic Data Collection Technology._  As you navigate through our Website, we may use automatic data collection technologies including Google Analytics to collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions, and patterns. This will generally include information about your location, your traffic pattern through our website, and any communications between your computer and our Website. Among other things, we will collect data about the type of computer you use, your Internet connection, your IP address, your operating system, and your browser type.

We use Facebook Pixel tracking software on our website for retargeting purposes when advertising our products and services through Facebook.

We may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.

 **What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

 **To personalize your experience**  
Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.

 **To improve our website**  
We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.

 **To improve customer service**  
Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.

 **To process transactions**  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

 **To send periodic emails**  
The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

 **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

 **How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be kept on file for more than 30 days.

 **Your Rights**

If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.

 **Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

 **Third Party Use of Cookies**

We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. The information they collect may be associated with your personal information or they may collect information, including personal information, about your online activities over time and across different websites and other online services. They may use this information to provide you with interest-based (behavioral) advertising or other targeted content.

These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

 **Third Party Links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

 **Email Policies**

All e-mails sent from our organization will clearly state who the e-mail is from and provide clear information on how to contact the sender. In addition, all e-mail messages will also contain concise information on how to remove yourself from our mailing list so that you receive no further e-mail communication from us.

 **Childrens’ Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

 **Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

 **Your Consent**

By using the Website or by clicking to accept or agree to the Terms of Use when this option is made available to you, you accept and agree to be bound and abide by our online Privacy Policy.

 **Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

This policy was last modified on 5/24/2018

 **Contacting us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us at info@addicted2success.com

#### TERMS OF USE

This website grants you a limited, personal, non-exclusive, non-transferable license to use our resources provided (in exchange for an email address)  for your own personal or internal business use. You have no right to modify, edit, copy, reproduce, create derivative works of, alter, enhance or in any way exploit any of this content in any manner. It also may not be sold or redistributed without the express written consent of the Company.

If you’d like to share ( _or link to_ ) our content, please be sure to give credit where credit is due. If you share our content, include our company name Addicted2Success (or Instagram handle @addicted2success). If you share an excerpt, include our full company name and a link back to the original page or post.

## – Information security

We work hard to protect our users from unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of information we hold however not website is entirely secure. You should protect the account information in your possession as well.

## – Third-Party Sites

Our Privacy Policy does not apply to services offered by other companies or individuals, including products or sites that may be displayed to you on this site. We also do not control the privacy policies and your privacy settings on third-party sites, including social networks.

## – Enforcement

We regularly review our compliance with our Privacy Policy. When we receive formal written complaints, we will contact the person who made the complaint to follow up.

## – Our Services are Located in Australia

Our website and associated services are hosted in Australia.

## – Changes

  *     *       *         * Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will post any privacy policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of privacy policy changes).This Privacy Policy was last updated on May 24th, 2018.
